One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Candy, candy... sluggie-uggie!
‫حلوى، حلوى... محار‬
Wave Room
‫غرفة الموج‬
What do you mean you're done for?! What's happening over there?!
‫ماذا تقصدين بحانت نهايتكم؟ ما الذي يجري عندكم؟‬
Hey, guys!
‫يا رفاق‬
If we get caught in that wave, we'll be done for!
‫سنهلك إن ابتلعتنا الموجة‬
Oh right! We have the Coup de Burst!
‫صحيح، لنستخدم الكودو باست‬
We can't use it! We don't have enough cola!
‫لا فائدة، ليس لدينا ما يكفي من الكولا‬
Pedro, I'm sorry! You sacrificed yourself to save us, but...
‫أعتذر يا بيدرو، ضحيت بنفسك من‬ ‫أجل إنقاذنا، لكن...‬
Everyone, listen!
‫استمعوا جميعًا‬
My cake!
‫كعكتي‬
Wait! Wait, wait!
‫مهلًا، مهلًا، مهلًا‬
Wait a minute, Mama!
‫انتظري قليلًا يا ماما‬
If you do that, the cake will sink into the sea, too!
‫على هذا المعدل ستغرق الكعكة في البحر أيضًا‬
Mama!
‫ماما‬
Hurry up!
‫أسرعوا‬
Okay!
‫حاضر‬
D-Does this look okay, Jinbe-san?!
‫أ-أهذا مناسب يا جينبي-سان؟‬
Yes, that's fine!
‫أجل، إنّه يفي بالغرض‬
But it's too reckless! You're trying to handle a ship's sails all on your own!
‫لكن هذا ضربٌ من الجنون‬ ‫إنّك تحاول التحكم بكل الأشرعة بيد واحدة‬
Nami! How is the wind?!
‫نامي، ماذا عن الرياح؟‬
A strong wind is coming from the south!
‫رياح قوية قادمة من الجنوب‬
All right!
‫حسنًا‬
What are you going to do, Jinbe?!
‫ما الذي تنوي فعله يا جينبي؟‬
I'm gonna tack this ship as fast as I can!
‫سأغيّر مسار السفينة حالًا‬
Are you joking?! Why do you want to turn the ship?!
‫أنت تمزح، لِمَ تودّ تغيير مسار السفينة؟‬
We're going to enter the green room!
‫سندخل الغرفة الخضراء‬
Here we go! Here we go!
‫هـ-ها نحن ذا‬
The green room?! What's that?!
‫الغرفة الخضراء؟ ما هذه بحقّك؟‬
Why are we heading toward the wave, Jinbe?!
‫لِمَ نتجه نحو الموجة يا جينبي؟‬
I see! This green room you're talking about must be heaven!
‫فهمت، إنّك تقصد الجنة بالغرفة الخضراء‬
Doctor! I'll be heading over to your side soon!
‫دكتور، إنني قادم لرؤيتك‬
It's over! This is impossible! We aren't surfing, you know!
‫قُضي علينا، يستحيل على السفينة ركوب الأمواج‬
Pedro!
‫بيدرو‬
Hold on tight to the ship!
‫تشبثوا بالسفينة جيّدًا‬
Splash!
‫تلطيخ‬
What's wrong?! What happened?!
‫ما الخطب؟ ماذا حدث؟‬
Hey, can you hear me?!
‫أنتم، أتسمعوني؟‬
Somebody! Say something!
‫ليجب أحدٌ ما‬
Is this heaven? It's beautiful...
‫أنحن في الجنة؟ ما أجملها...‬
This is a good ship!
‫يا لها من سفينة رائعة‬
The green room is found within surging waves. It is a room of waves that forms for a brief moment.
‫الغرفة الخضراء عبارة عن «غرفة الموج»‬ ‫التي تتشكل مؤقتًا داخل الموجة الساقطة‬
It has always been the perfect playground for fishman children!
‫بالنسبة لأطفال البرمائيين، إنّها المكان الأمتع للعب‬
Then, this place is...
‫إذًا هذا المكان...‬
...inside the wave?!
‫داخل الموجة؟‬
We're gonna sail through it! Hang on!
‫سنخرج قريبًا، تمسكوا‬
We have a good ship and a good navigator!
‫لديكم سفينة جيّدة وملّاحة بارعة‬
With a good helmsman, this ship will be invincible!
‫لذا إن تحكمتم بها جيّدًا، فستكون هذه السفينة لا تقهر‬
Amazing! He's controlling a sloop like it's part of his own body!
‫مذهل، إنّه يتحكم بالسفينة الشراعية كما لو أنّها أحد أطراف جسده‬
I've never seen such a helmsman before!
‫لم أرَ مثل هذا الرُبّان قط‬
You're amazing, Jinbe!
‫أنت مذهل يا جينبي‬
So we're not gonna die?!
‫لن نموت إذًا؟‬
Wedding...
‫كعكة...‬
Oh well... Serves you weaklings right!
‫لا يهم، نالوا ما يستحقونه أولئك الأوغاد‬
Lick!
‫بيرورين‬
This is Perospero.
‫معك بيروسبيرو‬
Hey, Katakuri.
‫يا كاتاكوري‬
Hey, Nami! Brook! Carrot!
‫نامي، بروك، كاروت‬
Oh dear!
‫عجبًا‬
We were just about to invade the ship!
‫كنّا على وشك اقتحام السفينة‬
The plan's canceled, guys!
‫أُلغيت الخطة يا رفاق‬
It seems like the ship has already sunk into the sea.
‫يبدو أنّ السفينة غرقت في البحر بالفعل‬
But it's strange, Big Sis.
‫لكن هذا غريب يا أختي‬
The other side of the mirror doesn't look like it's underwater.
‫الجانب الآخر من المرآة لا يبدو مغمورًا بالمياه‬
Look!
‫انظري‬
No way!
‫يستحيل حدوث هذا‬
But, just to make sure, shoot one more time.
‫لكن للتأكد لا أكثر، أطلقا سهمًا آخر‬
Wow! The mirror! Big Sis, it suddenly broke!
‫انكسرت، لقد انكسرت المرآة فجأة يا أختي‬
What? What? What's going on?!
‫ماذا؟ ماذا؟ ما الذي يجري؟‬
Nami-san ! Why did you break the mirror?!
‫نامي-سان، لِمَ كسرتِ المرآة؟‬
Luffy-san can't come back to the ship without it!
‫لا يستطيع لوفي-سان العودة إلى السفينة من دونها‬
Let me focus just on this guy!
‫لذا دعوني أركز على هذا الشخص فقط‬
Just break them all! Every single mirror on the ship!
‫لا بأس، حطموا جميع المرايا التي على متن السفينة‬
But...
‫لكن...‬
Do you want to get in Luffy's way?!
‫أتريدون إعاقة لوفي؟‬
These are our captain's orders! Hurry up!
‫إنّها أوامر القبطان، باشروا بتنفيذها‬
There are still some mirrors!
‫ما زال توجد بعض المرايا‬
I found one, Joscar!
‫عثرتُ على واحدة يا جوسكر‬
I found it, too, Mascar!
‫عثرتُ عليها أيضًا يا ماسكر‬
Let's do it, Joscar!
‫هيّا يا جوسكر‬
Let's do it, Mascar!
‫هيّا يا ماسكر‬
Make sure to find all the mirrors!
‫احرصوا على إيجاد مختلف أنواع المرايا‬
Shoot!
‫أطلقا‬
What's going on?!
‫ما الذي يحدث؟‬
This is the last one!
‫هذه الأخيرة‬
Are those guys alive?
‫أما زالوا على قيد الحياة؟‬
Big Bro Peros said they took care of them...
‫أخي الكبير بيروس قال أنّهم قضوا عليهم‬
I guess the ship sank and the mirrors were shattered by the water pressure, Joscar!
‫لا بدّ أنّ السفينة غرقت وتحطمت المرايا بسبب ضغط المياه يا جوسكر‬
Yeah, I guess that's it, Mascar!
‫أجل، لا بدّ أنّ هذا ما حدث يا ماسكر‬
Hey, Luffy!
‫يا لوفي‬
Are you all right?!
‫هل أنت بخير؟‬
Chopper!
‫تشوبر‬
I have something to tell you, so get away from the enemies!
‫نريد التحدث معك، لذا ابتعد عن الأعداء‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
Are you guys all right?!
‫هل أنتم بخير يا رفاق؟‬
Hey! Straw Hat is running away!
‫أنتم، قبعة القش يهمّ بالهروب‬
What happened?! The candy guy said the Sunny sank!
‫ما الذي حدث؟ رجل الحلوى قال إنّ سفينة الساني غرقت‬
We thought we were going to sink, too! But Jinbe did something amazing!
‫حتّى نحن ظننا أنّها ستغرق، لكن جينبي كان مذهلًا‬
We're all fine, Luffy!
‫نحن بخير يا لوفي‬
Luffy-san! We broke all the mirrors on the ship!
‫لوفي-سان، حطمنا جميع المرايا التي على السفينة‬
I see! Good job!
‫فهمت، هذا مطمئن‬
With this, our enemies won't be able to come here, but you won't be able to come back either!
‫صحيح أنّ العدو لا يمكنه الوصول إلينا الآن، لكن الأمر ينطبق عليك أيضًا‬
Yeah, that's okay! I'll figure out someth–
‫أجل، لا عليكم، سأجد حلًّا لهذا الأمر‬
No you won't! You don't even have a plan!
‫كلا، لن تجد، فأنت لا تملك خطة أصلًا‬
Listen carefully, Luffy!
‫أصغ إليّ يا لوفي‬
Sanji-kun is baking the cake on Cacao Island right now!
‫يخبز سانجي-كن الكعكة الآن على جزيرة الكاكاو‬
That's where we're heading!
‫وتلك الجزيرة هي وجهتنا‬
At the earliest, we'll arrive in 10 hours!
‫سنصل إلى هناك في غضون 10 ساعات تقريبًا‬
That's around one a.m.!
‫أي الواحدة صباحًا‬
So after you beat that guy up,
‫لذا بعد أن تبرح ذلك الشخص ضربًا...‬
search for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island! We'll meet you there!
‫ابحث عن المرآة التي تؤدي إلى جزيرة الكاكاو، وسنلتقي هناك‬
Damn! I can't get it off!
‫سحقًا، لا يمكنني نزعها‬
Is something wrong, Luffy?
‫ما الخطب يا لوفي؟‬
Can you hear me?
‫أتسمعني؟‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Hey! Stay focused!
‫حافظ على تركيزك‬
Maybe he's in trouble!
‫ربما وقع في مأزق‬
Please respond!
‫أجب علينا رجاءً يا لوفي‬
Are you okay, Luffy?!
‫هل أنت بخير يا لوفي؟‬
Luffy-san!
‫لوفي-سان‬
Willow Mochi!
‫ياناغي موتشي‬ ‫صفصاف الموتشي‬
Luffy?
‫لوفي؟‬
You're fine, right, Luffy-san?!
‫هل أنت على ما يرام يا لوفي-سان؟‬
What's the matter, Luffy?!
‫ما الخطب يا لوفي؟‬
Hurry up and get there, guys!
‫اذهبوا إلى هناك بسرعة يا رفاق‬
I'll probably be there soon, and I'll be tired of waiting!
‫فسأصل إلى هناك قريبًا، وسأشعر بالملل من الانتظار‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
See you later, guys!
‫أراكم لاحقًا يا رفاق‬
Our pursuers will be here soon! Let's keep an eye out!
‫مطاردينا سيصلون إلى هنا قريبًا، لذا لنبق يقظين‬
Roger!
‫عُلم‬
Let's go to the observation deck, Carrot!
‫لنتولّى المراقبة يا كاروت‬
Okay, Chobro!
‫حاضر يا تشونيكي‬
"I don't plan on dying in a place like this,"
‫«لن أموت هنا»‬
is what you'll say next.
‫أهذا كل ما لديك لتقوله...‬
Are those really your last words?
‫قبل أن تلقى حتفك؟‬
I don't plan on dying in a place like this!
‫لن أموت هنا‬
No one dies because they want to.
‫لا أحد يقرر الموت بمحض إرادته‬
Most people...
‫أغلب الأموات...‬
die against their will.
‫ماتوا رغم إرادتهم‬
He's right!
‫هذا صحيح، لماذا لا تستسلم وتلقى حتفك بهدوء يا قبعة القش؟‬
Branch!
‫يا فرع‬
The name's Brûlée!
‫اسمي بروليه‬
Don't think that you can beat him with just your spirit, brat!
‫لن تهزمه بالاعتماد على روحك القتالية فقط أيها الغِر‬
Big Brother Katakuri isn't just an undefeated man,
‫فأخي كاتاكوري ليس مجرّد رجل لا يقهر‬
he's a superhuman whose back has never once touched the ground since he was born!
‫إنّه شخصٌ خارق لم يلمس ظهره الأرض قط منذ ولادته‬
Stop it, Brûlée!
‫يكفي يا بروليه‬
The legend goes like this: The moment he was born,
‫يقال أنّه وقف على قدميه‬ ‫منذ اللحظة التي وُلد فيها ونام جالسًا على كرسي‬
He's never laid down in his life! He's a man who scorns even the ground!
‫لم يستلقي على ظهرة ولو لمرّة في حياته‬ ‫إنّه رجل يحتقر الأرض بحد ذاتها‬
He's always dignified...
‫لطالما كان ذو كبرياء‬
calm, and strong!
‫هادئ وقوي‬
He's the perfect human!
‫إنّه بشري مثالي من جميع النواحي‬
That's our big brother, Katakuri!
‫هذا هو أخينا الأكبر كاتاكوري‬
He's the Charlotte family's greatest creation!
‫إنّه أقوى أفراد عائلة شارلوت‬
So a small fry like you challenging him to a duel
‫لذا وضيع مثلك ليس مؤهلًا لمواجهته‬
Shut up! Go away!
‫اخرسي، انقلعي من هنا‬
What are you trying to do... to my little sister?!
‫ما الذي تحاول فعله بأختي؟‬
Big Brother!
‫أخي...‬
Mochi Thrust!
‫موتشي تسكي‬ ‫دفعة الموتشي‬
Ouch...
‫مؤلم...‬
That was close!
‫كان ذلك وشيكًا‬
I almost got crushed!
‫كدت أُسحق‬
The name of this spear is Mogura!
‫هذا الرُمح الثلاثي يُدعى موغورا‬
Your arms... or your legs? Which body part do you want removed first?
‫يداك أم قدماك؟ حدد أجزاء جسدك التي يمكنك الاستغناء عنها‬
I'll sever them for you!
‫وسأقطعها لك‬
Please start with his head, Big Bro!
‫أبدأ برأسه رجاءً يا أخي‬
Shut up, already!
‫اخرسي أيتها اللعينة‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Giant Rifle!
‫غيغانت رايفل‬ ‫البندقية العملاقة‬
I was listening!
‫كنتُ أستمع إليكم...‬
Straw Hat!
‫يا قبعة القش‬
I know about your meeting place.
‫عرفت المكان الذي تحاولون الالتقاء فيه‬
Do you wanna play with a wave again, Mama?
‫أتريدين اللعب بموجة أخرى يا ماما؟‬
At Sea Within the Territory
‫في البحر داخل إقليم بيغ مام‬
Come on! Let's do it!
‫هيّا، لنفعلها‬
Mama, are you listening?
‫أتسمعينني يا ماما؟‬
What?! Their ship hasn't sunk yet?!
‫ماذا؟ أما زالت سفينتهم تُبحر؟‬
Are you sure, Brûlée?!
‫هل أنتِ متأكدة يا بروليه؟‬
Yes, I heard their voices!
‫أجل، سمعت أصواتهم‬
But my candy monster swallowed them with a giant wave!
‫لكن وحش الحلوى صنع موجة عاتية وابتلعتهم‬
How did they escape?!
‫فكيف نجوا منها؟‬
I don't know how they did it!
‫لا أعلم كيف فعلوا ذلك‬
But they're definitely still alive! They'll be showing up on Cacao Island sometime tonight.
‫لكنهم على قيد الحياة بالفعل وسيظهرون حتمًا على جزيرة الكاكاو في منتصف الليل‬
That is what they promised Straw Hat Luffy. There's no mistake!
‫فهذا ما وعدوا قبعة القش به بلا أدنى شك‬
What they don't know is
‫وما لا يعرفونه هو...‬
that it's our final destination, too!
‫أنّها وجهتنا الأخيرة أيضًا‬
Mama! The cake you desire is at Chocolat Town on Cacao Island!
‫ماما، الكعكة التي تشتهينها‬ ‫موجودة في بلدة الشوكولاتة على جزيرة الكاكاو‬
Aren't you excited?
‫أليس هذا مشوّقًا؟‬
I lied to her out of desperation,
‫كذبتُ عليها لأنني كنتُ يائسًا‬
but if I take Mama there like this, I can cover up my lie!
‫لكن إن أخذتها إلى هناك بهذه الطريقة‬ ‫فسأتمكن من التستر على كذبتي تلك‬
Pudding is baking the cake on Cacao Island!
‫تُعدّ بودينغ الكعكة على جزيرة الكاكاو‬
No matter what happens, everything will be settled!
‫مهما حدث، فسيُحسم كل شيء هناك‬
Wedding cake!
‫كعكة الزفاف‬
Mama, it's that way, huh?!
‫ماما، أتودّين الذهاب إلى هناك؟‬
Wait a sec! That's Nuts Island!
‫تمهّل لحظة، هذه جزيرة المكسرات‬
Hey, hey, what are you doing?!
‫مهلًا، مهلًا، ما الذي تفعلينه؟‬
Mama! Their ship didn't go that way! The cake is on Cacao Island!
‫ماما، هذه ليست وجهة سفينتهم‬ ‫سيُوصلون الكعكة إلى جزيرة الكاكاو‬
Wedding cake!
‫كعكة الزفاف‬
No, Mama! Stop!
‫كلا يا ماما، توقفي‬
Don't go that way!
‫لا تذهبي إلى هناك‬
Mirro-world
‫عالم المرايا‬
He never learns!
‫إنّه لا يتعلّم أبدًا‬
You bastard!
‫أيها الوغد‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Grizzly Corkscrew Magnum!
‫غريزلي كوركسكرو ماغنوم‬ ‫المسدس الرمادي اللولبي‬
Damn!
‫سحقًا‬
He's always able to hit me when I dodge!
‫إنّه قادر على إصابتي بدقة مهما تفاديته‬
That tires me out even more!
‫هذا مرهق للغاية‬
It's the same for me.
‫أشاركك الشعور ذاته‬
Nobody has ever dodged my attacks like you have.
‫فلم يسبق أن واجهت شخصًا يراوغ الكثير من هجماتي‬
It's stressful!
‫هذا يرهقني‬
You tried to take Mogura away from me...
‫حاولت أخذ موغورا منّي؟‬
Damn! I almost got it!
‫سحقًا، كدت أحصل عليه‬
Flowing Mochi!
‫ناغاري موتشي‬ ‫تدفق الموتشي‬
The ground became mochi !
‫تحولت الأرضية إلى موتشي‬
This is just like what Doflamingo did!
‫مثلما فعل دوفلامينغو حينذاك‬
Listen up, fledgling!
‫اسمع أيها المبتدئ‬
Devil fruit abilities have yet another stage to them, called "awakening"!
‫قدرات فواكه الشيطان‬ ‫لها مرحلة أخرى تُدعى «الإيقاظ»‬
Of course my ability is awakened.
‫بالطبع، فقد أيقظتُ قدرتي‬
Oh, no!
‫هذا سيئ‬
It's no use.
‫لا فائدة‬
With your elasticity and viscosity, you can't move anymore.
‫لن تقدر على التحرك بعد تقييدك بمرونة ولزوجة قدرتي‬
Should I just chop you up?
‫أيجدر بي تمزيقك؟‬
Or should I let you suffocate in the mochi ?
‫أم أدعك تختنق داخل الموتشي؟‬
How would you like to die?
‫بأي طريقة تودّ أن تموت؟‬
I'm not gonna die!
‫أنا لن أموت‬
Gear Fourth?
‫غير فورث؟‬
How interesting.
‫مثير للاهتمام‬
Whole Cake Island (Sweet City)
‫جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة‬ ‫(مدينة الحلوى)‬
How odd...
‫هذا غريب...‬
We haven't gotten a report on the location of the Straw Hats' ship.
‫لم نتلقَّ أي مستجدات بشأن موقع‬ ‫سفينة طاقم قبعة القش...‬
What are the territorial sea slugs doing?!
‫ما الذي تفعله رخويات الإقليم البحري؟‬
Shut up, Pekoms!
‫اخرس يا بيكومز‬
Just stop crying already!
‫إلى متى ستستمر بالبكاء؟‬
Big Bro Pedro!
‫أخي بيدرو‬
I feel pity for him...
‫أشعر بالشفقة عليه...‬
It's hard to believe that your
‫صديق طفولته الذي كان‬ ‫بمثابة الأخ له قرر الموت عبر تفجير نفسه-بون‬
He was our enemy!
‫كان عدوّنا‬
Bon...
‫بون‬
It's pointless to die here! The day of the new dawn is coming!
‫لا فائدة من الموت هنا، ففجر العالم قد اقترب‬
I must go back to my country!
‫يجب أن أعود إلى موطني‬
This will break all of your magic spells, right?
‫هذا سيمحو كل تعاويذك السحرية، أليس كذلك؟‬
Bombs?!
‫قنابل؟‬
Farewell.
‫الوداع‬
It was a shock to me as well-amour...
‫حتّى أنا صُدمت أيضًا-آمور...‬
Five years ago, I witnessed Pedro begging for his life, tears and all-bon.
‫فقد رأيت بيدرو منذ خمس سنوات يبكي متوسلًا للعتق عن حياته-بون‬
And that same man sacrificed his life to allow them to sail away!
‫والآن الرجل نفسه فضّل التضحية بحياته لمساعدتهم على الإبحار‬
Who cares?
‫وماذا في ذلك؟‬
Big Bro...
‫أخي...‬
We may still be underestimating Straw Hat Luffy-issant !
‫ربما يعني ذلك أننا ما زلنا نستهين بقبعة القش-إسّن‬
What's your point?
‫ماذا تقصد؟‬
My point is that we should take this more seriously-bon !
‫أقصد ينبغي لنا أن نكون حذرين منه-بون‬
Mama will never be taken out by a brat like him!
‫يستحيل أن تُهزم ماما أمام غِر مثله‬
Are you saying that Straw Hat Luffy is that much weaker than her?
‫أتقصد أنّ قبعة القش لوفي أضعف من أن يفعل ذلك؟‬
Of course! As a pirate, she's in a different class!
‫بالطبع، إنّه قرصان ليس بمستوانا‬
Can you say the same even while looking at Mama's fallen castle?!
‫أما زلت تقول ذلك بينما قصر ماما محطّم أمام عينيك؟‬
That happened by chance!
‫كانت مجرّد حادثة مصادفة‬
An accident you say?! And are the sea slugs neglecting their security duties by chance as well?!
‫إن كانت حادثة مصادفة فهل فشل الرخويات في تأدية دورها الأمني حادثة مصادفة أيضًا؟‬
What?! Are you telling me that all of this is part of their plan as well?!
‫ماذا إذًا؟ أتقصد أنّ كل هذا ضمن خطتهم؟‬
At the very least,
‫على الأقل، منذ وصول طاقم قبعة القش‬ ‫توالت الحوادث المفاجئة علينا-جيور‬
Arrogant rulers will have the rug pulled out from under them.
‫المسيطر المتغطرس» سيُطاح به»‬
To prevent the one-in-a-million chance that Mama's name is tarnished,
‫لمنع أدنى فرصة من شأنها أن تشوّه سمعة ماما يجدر بنا نشر أقوى أساطيلنا في جميع أنحاء منطقتنا-آمور‬
Minister Mont d'Or.
‫مونت دور-ساما‬
There's a call from Minister Custard on the transponder snail.
‫وردك اتصال من حلزون اتصال كاسترد-ساما‬
Custard was chasing after Bege, wasn't she?
‫كانت كاسترد تُطارد بيجي، صحيح؟‬
This is Mont d'Or. Did you take care of Bege?
‫معكِ مونت دور، هل تولّيتِ أمر بيجي؟‬
Well...
‫في الواقع...‬
We lost track of his ship.
‫فقدنا أثر سفينتهم‬
What?!
‫ماذا قلتِ؟‬
The territorial sea slugs aren't sending us the location of the ship!
‫رخويات الإقليم البحري لم ترسل لنا إحداثيات موقع سفينتهم‬
Huh?! It's not just us?!
‫ماذا؟ ليس نحن فقط؟‬
We haven't gotten the location of the Straw Hats, either!
‫حتّى نحن لم نتلقَّ إحداثيات موقع سفينة طاقم قبعة القش‬
Are you serious?!
‫ماذا قلت؟‬
In any case, look for Bege! Listen! Don't let him get away, no matter what!
‫علي أي حال، اعثري على بيجي‬
I understand!
‫مفهوم‬
Hey! Check on them right away!
‫أنتِ، تحققي من الأمر حالًا‬
I'm telling you to check up on the territorial sea slugs on the sea floor!
‫تفقدي رخويات الإقليم في قاع البحر‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضرة‬
What the hell is happening down there?!
‫ما الذي يحدث بالضبط؟‬
Nostra Castello: "Our Castle" in Italian The Nostra Castello At Sea
‫نوسترا كاستيلو تعني «قلعتنا» بالإيطالية‬ ‫سفينة نوسترا كاستيلو في البحر‬
I was expecting more of them to chase us!
‫توقعتهم سيواصلون مطاردتنا لأبعد من ذلك‬
What's going on?
‫فما الذي يحدث يا تُرى؟‬
Maybe they're not tracking our location-rero.
‫ربما لم تصلهم إحداثيات موقعنا-ريرو‬
The territorial sea slugs?
‫رخويات البحر؟‬
Rero.
‫ريرو‬
If there are territorial sea slugs, then the transponder snails should react.
‫يُفترض أن ترسل لهم رخويات البحر‬ ‫إحداثيات موقعنا عبر حلزون الاتصال‬
But they're silent-rero.
‫لكن يبدو أنّه لم يصلهم شيء-ريرو‬
I've never heard of anything like this!
‫لم يسبق أن سمعت عن هذا الأمر قط‬
But that's great. Keep it at maximum speed!
‫لكن هذا من حسن حظنا، لنستغل ذلك بالانطلاق‬
Hurry to Cacao Island!
‫بسرعة نحو جزيرة الكاكاو‬
Let's take the shortest route to pick up Chiffon!
‫لنسلك أقصر طريق لأخذ شيفون معنا‬
– Yeah! – Rero!
‫حاضر -‬ ‫ريرو -‬
This is Nusstorte, speaking from Germa's ship. Nusstorte: "Engadiner Nusstorte", a Swiss nut tart
‫معك نوستورت، أُحدثك من سفينة جيرما‬
Big Brother! How did things go with Germa?!
‫أخي، كيف سار الأمر مع جيرما؟‬
We crushed them with 10,000 soldiers. Their kingdom has been devastated!
‫سحقناهم بعشرة آلاف جندي ودمرنا مملكتهم على بكرة أبيها‬
As expected! But you shouldn't go overboard like that...
‫كما هو متوقع منك، لكنك بالغت قليلًا‬
With our strength, it was a piece of cake...
‫كان الأمر سهلًا للغاية نظرًا لقوتنا‬
By the way, Big Brother...
‫بالمناسبة يا أخي...‬
Kingdom of Germa
‫مملكة جيرما‬
You didn't destroy their cloning system, did you?
‫أنتم لم تدمروا نظام صنع الجنود المستنسخون، صحيح؟‬
Of course not. That's what we came here for.
‫بالطبع، فذلك ما كنا نسعى إليه منذ البداية‬
That's the least we could do!
‫هذا هو المطلوب‬
Damn Germa! They were doomed the moment we had them in our sights!
‫أولئك الجيرما، حُكم عليهم بالهلاك‬ ‫في اللحظة التي وضعناهم نصب أعيننا‬
What happened to the Straw Hats?
‫ما الذي حلّ بطاقم قبعة القش؟‬
Actually, we accidentally let them get away.
‫بصراحة، لقد أبحروا‬
They're heading due west...
‫إنّهم يحاولون الهرب باتجاه الغرب‬
Well, it's only a matter of time before we get them.
‫لكنها مسألة وقت حتّى نقبض عليهم‬
I'll leave it to you!
‫سأدع الأمر لكم‬
Yeah, good job!
‫أجل، بوركت جهودك‬
And that's how you do it...
‫هكذا الأمر إذًا...‬
So Luffy-kun and the others are okay.
‫إذًا لوفي-كن والآخرون بخير؟‬
What should we do now?
‫والآن، ماذا سنفعل؟‬
Let's go! Set sail!
‫هيّا بنا، استعدوا للإبحار‬
Roger!
‫عُلم‬
Muscle Balloon!
‫كينيكو فوسين‬ ‫بالون العضلات‬
Why should I stand here and watch...
‫أعلم مسبقًا أنّك تنوي زيادة قوتك‬
when I already know that you're going to power up?
‫فلِمَ عساي سأكتفي بمشاهدتك تفعل ذلك؟‬
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
‫يا قبعة القش لوفي‬
I'll tell you this now...
‫أؤكد لك أنني لا أستهين بك إطلاقًا‬
Mirror Mochi!
‫كاغامي موتشي‬ ‫مرآة الموتشي‬
What? That's mochi ?!
‫ماذا؟ تلك موتشي أيضًا؟‬
This is bad! If I get crushed under all that mochi, I'll be buried alive!
‫هذا سيئ، سأدفن حيًّا إن سقطت عليّ‬
Yes, you'll suffocate.
‫أجل، ستختنق‬
This is where you die!
‫هذه نهايتك‬
I'm sorry that the fight has to end like this, but it's made me a little irritated.
‫المعذرة على إنهاء النزال بهذه الطريقة، فقد ضجرت من الأمر‬
Because you held on for much longer than expected,
‫استغرقت وقتًا طويلًا في التعامل معك‬
I'm 40 minutes late for today's merienda. Merienda: Spanish word for a light meal
‫لذا تأخرت اليوم 40 دقيقة عن تناول الميريندا‬ ‫ميريندا = كلمة إسبانية تعني وجبة خفيفة‬
The suffering won't last long...
‫لن تدوم معاناتك طويلًا‬
Farewell, Straw Hat...
‫الوداع يا قبعة القش‬